Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2 Locals, 2.
  - Local 272
    - Local 272 Factionalism and Exide, October 4, 1943-October 9, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 101)
      - Emspak to Linsley, October 9, 1944; 8.
    - Local 272 Maxwell, Manning and Moore Strike, September 28-October 10, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 102)
      - Donald Tormey Telegram to Julius Emspak, September 28, 1945; 1.
      - Tormey Telegram to Emspak, October 5, 1945; 2.
      - Report of Strike, October 5, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Tormey, October 8, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Paul Seymour, October 8, 1945; 5.
      - Tormey to Seymour, October 10, 1945; 6.
    - Local 272 Correspondence and Charter Application, June 9, 1941-April 4, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 103)
      - Charter Application, June 9, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Linsley Regarding Factionalism with October 8, 1941, Arthur Ring Letter to UE, October 9, 1941; 2.
      - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Local 272 Exide Amalgamations, May 11, 1942; 3.
      - Benjamin Leven Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 272 Cole Hersee Strikes, June 16, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Linsley Regarding Supplies, August 20, 1942; 5.
      - Linsley to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 16, 1942; 6.
      - Linsley to James Matles Regarding Local 272 Decca Contracts, March 20, 1943; 7.
      - Donald Tormey to Emspak Regarding Manning, Mazwell and More Supplies, June 4, 1945; 8.
      - Cole Hersee Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 272 Cole Hersee Strikes, April 4, 1946; 9.
  - Local 273
    - Local 273 Officers Lists, January 1947-January 1948 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Local 273 Incoming Correspondence, November 10, 1941-January 7, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 105)
      - Julius Emspak to Roger Fournier Regarding Mailing List, November 10-25, 1941; 1-2.
      - Emspak to Fournier, May 1, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Fournier Regarding Finances, February 7, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Fournier Regarding Veterans and Dues, August 20, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Fournier Regarding Local 273 Strikes, July 31, 1946; 6.
      - Emspak to Peter Boucher Regarding Per Capita, January 17, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Maurice Lafluer Regarding Political Action Committee, January 7, 1948; 8.
    - Local 273 Outgoing Correspondence, November 12, 1941-February 7, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - Frank Ackstin to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, August 3, 1947; 1.
      - Roger Fournier to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Mailing List, November 12, 1941; 2.
      - Fournier to Emspak Regarding Overtime, November 23, 1942; 3.
      - Fournier to UE Regarding Mailing List, August 2, 1945; 4.
      - Fournier to UE Regarding Local 273 Strikes, August 1, 1946; 5.
      - Maurice Lafleur to Paul Seymour Regarding Political Action Committee, 6.
      - Charles Manning to UE Regarding PAC, February 7, 1948; 7.
    - Local 273 Correspondence, May 13, 1977-December 21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Local 273 Financial, 1941-1948 (Box 13, Folder 108)
      - Roger Fournier Salary and Expence Letter, November 18, 1941; 1.
      - Ledger, 1946-1948; 2.
    - Local 273 Contracts, March 22-April 1, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 109)
      - William Mackesy to James Matles, March 22, 1943; 1.
      - Matles to Mackesy, April 1, 1943; 2.
    - Local 273 Strike, June 7-July 31, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 110)
      - Julius Emspak to Paul Seymour, June 7, 1946; 1.
      - Seymour to Emspak, June 11-July 9, 1946; 2-3.
      - Donald Tormey to James matles, July 31, 1946; 4.
    - Local 273 Strike, Subsidies and Other Monies, August 11, 1980-April 21, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Local 273 Correspondence and Charter Application, June 25, 1941-May 1, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 112)
      - Charter Application, June 25, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Linsley Regarding Overtime with April 27, 1942, Roger Fournier Letter to UE, May 1, 1942; 2.
    - Local 273 Bennington Eagle Square Stanley Tool, October 2, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Local 274
    - Local 274 Incoming Correspondence, July 25, 1941-August 20, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 114)
      - Janet Barish to Dorothy Archambo Regarding Staff Finances, October 28, 1953; 1.
      - Neil Brant to Albert Lambert Regarding Executive Order 9240, War Labor Board and Overtime, May 24, 1943; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Lambert Regarding Greenfield Tap and Die, July 25, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Gertrude Conrad Regarding District Two Officers, December 13, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Lambert Regarding Veterans and Dues, February 20, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Lambert Regarding Finances, March 7, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Conrad Regarding Finances, March 26, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Lambert Regarding Veterans and Dues, April 16, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Lambert Regarding Finances, April 17, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to Lambert Regarding Veterans and Dues, July 6, 1945; 10.
      - Emspak to Daniel Nadeau Regarding Finances, January 28, 1954; 11.
      - Emspak to Local 274 Members Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Strikes and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 3, 1954; 12.
      - Emspak to Nadeau Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Strikes and IUE Inter-union Rivalry with Februray 3, 1954, Emspak Letter to Local 274 Members, February 16, 1954; 13.
      - Emspak to Nadeau Regarding UE News and Membership, August 20, 1954; 14.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Lambert Regarding Finances, November 13, 1944; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Clifford McAvoy, December 8 ,1949; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Nadeau Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Collective Bargaining and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 22, 1953; 17.
      - James Matles to John Murphy Regarding Strike Fund, September 12, 1953; 18.
      - Don Pinkston to Helen Barber Regarding Publicity, August 20, 1945; 19.
      - UE to Helen Matus Regarding Finances, December 10, 1945; 20.
    - Local 274 Outgoing Correspondence, November 19, 1942-May 21, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 115)
      - Dorothy Archambo to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, May 21, 1953; 1.
      - Archambo to Barish Regarding 1953 UE Convention and Supplies, October 14, 1953; 2.
      - Helen Barber to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 26, 1946; 3.
      - Gertrude Conrad to UE Regarding Local 274 Officers, November 5, 1943; 4.
      - Conrad to Emspak Regarding Local 274 Officers, December 3, 1943; 5.
      - Edith Hammer to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 11, 1942; 6.
      - Hammer to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 19, 1942; 7.
      - Albert Lambert to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action Committee, November 14, 1944; 8.
      - Lambert to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 16, 1945; 9.
      - Lambert to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, February 17, 1945; 10.
      - Lambert to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 13, 1945; 11.
      - Lambert to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Dues, April 13-June 30, 1945; 12-13.
      - Lambert Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Strikes, November 6, 1945; 14.
      - Lambert to Paul Seymour Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, June 12, 1946; 15.
      - Lambert to Seymour Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, October 10, 1946; 16.
      - Helen Matus to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 29, 1945; 17.
      - Matus to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 10, 1945; 18.
      - Clifford McAvoy to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 7, 1949; 19.
      - James Mooney to UE Regarding Factionalism and Local 274 Officers Elections, December 18, 1943; 20.
      - Mooney to UE Regarding Factionalism, Local 274 Officers and Seniority, January 15, 1944; 21.
    - Local 274 Outgoing Correspondence, May 2, 1942-August 18, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 116)
      - Daniel Nadeau Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding 1948 UE Convention, July 30, 1948; 1.
      - Nadeau to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 13, 1951; 2.
      - Nadeau to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 9, 1952; 3.
      - Nadeau to Julius Emspak Regarding National Strike Fund, October 20, 1952; 4.
      - Nadeau to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strikes, November 13, 1952; 5.
      - Nadeau to Emspak Regarding Local 274 Strikes and Finances, January 21, 1954; 6.
      - Nadeau to Ray Klausner Regading Local 274 Officers, January 29, 1954; 7.
      - Nadeau to Emspak Regarding Finances and UE News, August 18, 1954; 8.
      - Ralph Streeter to Emspak Regarding Local 274 Officers, May 2, 1942; 9.
    - Local 274 Correspondence, November 9, 1967- November 5, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Local 274 Salary and Expense Letters, Ralph Streeter, October 9, 1941-January 9, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Local 274 Organization, June 1941-January 1942 (Box 13, Folder 119)
      - Charter Application, June 1, 1941; 1.
      - Departments' Possible Votes Analysis, January 1942; 2.
    - Local 274 Greenfield Wesco Tap and Die, February 13, 1980-April 21, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Local 274 Greenfield Correspondence, February 15, 1956-September 26, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die lambert vs. Nadeau, June 1, 1941-March 22, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Local 274 Strike Contributions, May 3-September 15, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Local 274 Subsidies and Other Monies, September 28, 1956-March 8, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Local 274 Subsidies and Other Monies, July 11, 1968-Februray 18, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Local 274 Legislative Committee and Political Action, April 26, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Local 274 Correspondence, Notification and Minutes, August 1941-January 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Walter Mugford Telegram to UE Regarding Spragues Organization, August 21, 1942; 1.
      - Greenfield Tap and Die Negotiation Minutes, November 5, 1942; 2.
      - James Matles Telegram to Gerard Steinberg Regarding Local 274 Strikes, November 6, 1947; 3.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Threadwell Tap and Die, May 5, 1947; 4.
      - Clifford McAvoy Telegram to James Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 21, 1949; 5.
      - Daniel Nadeau to Julius Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, November 5, 1953; 6.
      - Hugh Harley to Matles Regarding Local 274 Greenfield Tap and Die Strikes, January 1954; 7.
    - Local 274 Newspaper Clippings (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - "Plan 2 Union Official Charges Outside Meddling", 1.
      - "CIO Leaders See New Election at GTD's Plant 2", 2.
  - Local 275
    - Local 275 Officers Lists, December 1943-January 1953 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Local 275 Incoming Correspondence, February 4, 1946-July 1, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Julius Emspak to F. A. Rennick Regarding Veterans and Dues, February 4, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Elbert Calef Regarding Finances, June 27, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Calef Regarding Local 275 Turner Tanning Machine Strike, October 31, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Local 275 Strike Committee Regarding Finances, November 12, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Local 275 Strike Committee Regarding Local 275 Strikes, November 21, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Calef Regarding Local 275 Strikes, December 2, 1946-February 3, 1947; 6-12.
      - Emspak to Calef Regarding Per Capita, November 10, 1950; 13.
      - Emspak to Calef Regarding Finances, March 26, 1951-May 18, 1953; 14-15.
      - Emspak to Calef Regarding Local 275 Strikes, July 1, 1955; 16.
    - Local 275 Outgoing Correspondence, February 1942-May 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Elbert Calef to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 275 Strikes, January 18, 1947; 1.
      - Calef to UE Regarding Finances, October 29, 1947; 2.
      - Calef to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 7, 1949-November 6, 1950; 3-5.
      - Calef to Emspak Regarding Finances and Dues, March 15, 1951; 6.
      - Calef to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strikes, October 22, 1952; 7.
      - Calef to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 14, 1953; 8.
      - Charles Quellette to UE Regarding Address, February 8, 1942; 9.
      - Calef to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 17, 1955; 10.
      - Quellette to UE Regarding Finances, February 21, 1942; 11.
      - Quellette to UE Regarding Local 275 Officers and Constitutions, January 11, 1943; 12.
      - Quellette to UE Regarding Local 275 Officers, October 6, 1943; 13.
      - F. A. Rennick to UE Regarding Supplies, February 3, 1946; 14.
      - Louis Swinivch to UE Regarding Address Change, May 1956; 15.
      - Swinivch Telegram to UE Regarding Local 275 Strikes, January 8, 1947; 16.
    - Local 275 Correspondence, May 18, 1976-October 30, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Local 275 Bonding, January-June 1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Questionnaire, January 1942; 1.
      - Form, June 11, 1942; 2.
    - Local 275 Organization, August 1940-August 1941 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Richard Linsley Telegram to James Matles, September 5, 1940; 1.
      - Linsley Memo, August 1940; 2.
      - Charter Application, August 15, 1941; 3.
    - Local 275 New Britain Viking Aluminum, May 11-21, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Local 275 Strike, July 25-December 18, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Local 275 Notice of Labor Dispute, July 25, 1946; 1.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, August 1946; 2.
      - Julius Emspak Secretary to Paul Seymour, July 29, 1946; 3.
      - Report of Strike, August 30, 1946; 4.
      - Seymour to Emspak, October 23, 1946; 5.
      - Jake Zeramby to James Matles, October 28, 1946; 6.
      - Louis Swinivch to Emspak, December 11, 1946; 7.
      - Emspak to Don Tormey, December 16, 1946; 8.
      - Tormey to Emspak, December 18, 1946; 9.
    - Local 275 Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Don Tormey Regarding Locak 275 Strikes, February 17, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Local 275 Leaflet, "SOS-DIDO" Regarding Wages, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 276
    - Local 276 Officers Lists, January 1944-January 1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - List, January 1944; 1.
      - List with R. Fisher Letter to Julius Emspak, February 1944; 2.
      - Lists, April 1, 1947-January 19, 1949; 3-9.
    - Local 276 Incoming Correspondence, April 30, 1942-October 8, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Joseph Dermody to Joseph Messina Regarding Wages and White Collar Workers, October 2, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest Gosselin Regarding Finances, April 30, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Gosselin Regarding Supplies and Wages, July 13, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Louis Tino Regarding Local 276 Officers, January 28, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to Joseph Blair Regarding Stewards, May 6, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Ruth Fisher Regarding Meriden Organization, March 11, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Blair Regarding International Silver Company, January 20, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak Telegram to E. J. Massina Regarding Local 276 Banquet, January 29, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Janet Bernski Regarding Per Capita, January 17, 1947; 9.
      - Emspak to Blair Regarding Veterans and Dues, February 3, 1947; 10.
      - Emspak to Michael Tabellione Regarding Political Action Committee, December 2, 1947-January 7, 1948; 11-12.
      - Emspak to Tabellione Regarding Finances, March 30, 1948; 13.
      - Emspak to Stanley Szczupski Regarding Supplies and Dues, September 23, 1948; 14.
      - James Matles to Tabellione, October 8, 1948; 15.
      - David Scribner to Blair Regarding Grievances and Executive Order 9240, August 30, 1945; 16.
      - Joseph Turkowski to Blair Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 17.
      - Turkowski Telegram to Blair Regarding Grievances, September 14, 1944; 18.
    - Local 276 Outgoing Correspondence, May 5, 1942-October 13, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Joseph Blair to UE Regarding Meriden General Electric Foremen, March 26, 1943; 1.
      - Blair to Julius Emspak Regarding Grievances and Stewards, April 28, 1943; 2.
      - Blair to Emspak Regarding Meriden, January 14, 1945; 3.
      - Ruth Fisher to Emspak Regarding Local 276 Officers, August 18, 1944; 4.
      - Ernest Gosseler to UE Regarding Finances, May 5, 1942; 5.
      - Ernest to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Wages, July 7, 1942; 6.
      - E. J. Messina Telegram to UE, February 22, 1943; 7.
      - Messina Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 276 Banquet, January 26, 1945; 8.
      - Stanley Szcyupski to Emspak Regarding Supplies, September 20, 1948; 9.
      - Michael Tabellione to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 19, 1948; 10.
      - Tabellione to James Matles Regarding 1946 Strikes and Factionalism, August 12, 1948; 11.
      - Tabellione to Matles Regarding Factionalism, October 13, 1948; 12.
      - Louis Tina to Emspak Regarding Dues, June 17, 1943; 13.
      - Tina to UE Regarding Finances, December 20, 1944; 14.
    - Local 276 Correspondence, November 15,1967-September 23, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Local 276 Correspondence, May 2, 1968-December 6, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Local 276 Bonding, May 1942 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Questionnaire, May 1942; 1.
      - Form, May 11, 1942; 2.
    - Local 276 Supply Requisition, February 18, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Local 276 Organization, August 14-25, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Charter Application, August 14, 1941; 1.
      - Joseph Caiazza to James Matles, August 23, 1941; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Caiazza, August 25, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to A. J. Fitzgerald, August 25, 1941; 4.
    - Local 276 Athol Union Twist Drill, February 13, 1980-May 31, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Local 276 Athol Correspondence, July 19-November 15, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Local 276 Grievances, June 22-27, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Martin Hourihan to Julius Emspak, June 22, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Hourihan, June 27, 1942; 2.
    - Local 276 Strike, May 13-17, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Memo to Julius Emspak, May 13, 1943; 1.
      - James Matles Telegram to Joseph Massina, May 13, 1943; 2.
      - Joseph Caiazza Telegram to Matles, May 13, 1943; 3.
      - Caiazza to Matles with Merideu General Electric Walkout Report, May 17, 1943; 4.
    - Local 276 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Local 276 Factionalism, October 8, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - James Matles to Albert Smith with August 12, 1948, Michael Tabellione Letter to Matles, October 8, 1948; 1.
      - Matles to Paul Seymour, October 8, 1948; 2.
    - Local 276 Legislative Committee and Political Action, August 23, 1971-February 8, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Local 276 Correspondence, April 9, 1942-July 19, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Martin Hourhan to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 9, 1942; 1.
      - Joseph Caiazza to James Matles Regarding Guards, War Department and Organization, July 20, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Charles Rivers Regarding Meriden with March 1944, Ruth Fisher Letter to Emspak, March 11, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Albert Smith Regarding Plant Closure and Local 276 Officers with June 6, 1949, Louis Lentini Letter to Emspak, July 19, 1949; 4.
  - Local 277
    - Local 277 Officers Lists (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Local 277 Incoming Philip Madeinos Correspondence, July 2, 1942-November 23, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Neil Brant Regarding Grievances and Arbitrations, January 26, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding 1942 UE Convention, July 20, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 3, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak's Secretary, February 8, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, March 11, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 19, 1944-March 26, 1945; 6-8.
      - Albert Fitzgerald's Secretary, January 22, 1943-November 14, 1945; 9-11.
      - Fitzgerald's Secretary Regarding Local 277 Movie Twist Drill, November 23, 1945; 12.
      - Nat Geller Regarding Finances, July 2, 1942; 13.
      - Geller Regarding Supplies, July 3, 1942; 14.
      - James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 13, 1943; 15.
      - Matles Regarding War Rally and Staff Finances, January 25, 1943; 16.
      - Matles Regarding Navy Department and War Labor Board, January 25, 1943; 17.
      - Constance Van Oyen Regarding Arbitration, March 9, 1945; 18.
    - Local 277 Outgoing Philip Madeinos Correspondence, June 30, 1942-November 13, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Philip Madeinos to Nat Geller Regarding Supplies, June 30, 1942; 1.
      - Madeinos to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 277 Officers, July 15-August 7, 1942; 2-3.
      - Madeinos to James Matles Regarding Navy "E" War Production Council and Grievances, December 28, 1942; 4.
      - Madeinos to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding War Rally, January 21, 1943; 5.
      - Madeinos to Matles Regarding Staff Finances and War Rally, January 23, 1943; 6.
      - Madeinos to Matles Regarding War Rally, Arbitration and War Labor Board, February 5, 1943; 7.
      - Madeinos to Emspak Regarding American Aero-Marine Mendell Electric Manufacturing, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Arbitration and War Labor Board, May 1, 1943; 8.
      - Madeinos to Matles Regarding Local 277 Morse Twist Drill Collective Bargaining and War Labor Board, May 6, 1945; 9.
      - Madeinos to Emspak Regarding Finances, Arbitration and War Labor Board, February 1944; 10.
      - Madeinos to Emspak Regarding Supplies, WLB and Finances, April 4, 1944; 11.
      - Madeinos to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 277 Morse Twist Drill, National Labor Relations Board and WLB with Madeinos Letter to Mr. Schwellenbach, November 13, 1945; 12.
    - Local 277 Incoming Correspondence, December 30, 1942-March 31, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Julius Emspak Telegram to John Bandarra Regarding Supplies, April 17, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Seth Lovejoy Regarding Political Action Committee, November 14, 1947-February 6, 1948; 2-3.
      - Emspak to John Bandarra Regarding New Bedford, April 2, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Bandarra Regarding Our Lives, December 29, 1948; 5.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Bandarra, May 8, 1947; 6.
      - Fitzgerald to Bandarra Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and Factionalism, March 2, 1948; 7.
      - James Matles to Joseph Sylvia, December 30, 1942; 8.
      - Matles to Edwin Silviera Regarding Banquet Officers, March 31, 1955; 9.
    - Local 277 Outgoing Correspondence, February 3, 1942-January 31, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - John Bandarra to James Matles Regarding Factionalism, Staff Members and War Production Council, February 3, 1942; 1.
      - Bandarra to Dick Regarding Factionalism and Staff Membership, March 22, 1942; 2.
      - Bandarra to UE Regarding Mailing List, April 11, 1942; 3.
      - Bandarra to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, January 21, 1943; 4.
      - Bandarra to Julius Emspak Regarding Address, April 26, 1943; 5.
      - Bandarra to Matles Regarding Mailing Address, April 27, 1943; 6.
      - Bandarra Telegram to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 15, 1947; 7.
      - Bandarra to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 277 Officers, May 7, 1947; 8.
      - Bandarra Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, January 31, 1948; 9.
      - Bandarra to Emspak Regarding St. George Manufacturing Ace Cabinet, March 9, 1948; 10.
      - Bandarra to Emspak Regarding Publicity, December 27, 1948; 11.
      - Bandarra to Emspak Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strikes, February 4, 1949; 12.
      - Bandarra to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 277 St. George Manufacturing Strikes, January 31, 1950; 13.
      - Seth Lovejoy to UE Regarding Finances, July 17, 1947; 14.
      - Lovejoy to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 12, 1947-January 26, 1948; 15-16.
      - Joseph O'Brian to UE Regarding PAC, October 23, 1946; 17.
      - Elinore Parnes to Emspak Regarding PAC, September 6, 1946; 18.